{
    "id": "87d5c090ac4849ddbd7a63c778b77310",
    "title": "So, such, very, too: grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "9b8d5080b9b84e3f9a17fb3b81abe3d2",
            "title": "So, Such, Very, Too",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "It was …………………. hot that we didn’t go out.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "such",
                        "very"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is ……………….. old to work.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "very",
                        "too",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The tea was …………………. hot.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "very",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The milk was …………………. good that we couldn’t stop drinking it.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "very",
                        "too",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "It’s ………………… terrible weather.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "so",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is looking ………………….. older.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "so much",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was ………………….. warm when we were in Vienna.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "very",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He spoke ………………… fast that nobody could understand.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "very",
                        "too"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Would you be ………………….. kind as to tell me the time?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "very",
                        "too"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is a ………………….. intelligent child.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "very",
                        "so",
                        "too"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}